Jobs With Justice records 6369
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series II. Regional Coalitions
  - Mid-West Coalitions
    - Wisconsin
      - Campaign for a Sustainable Milwaukee, 1994-1997 (Box 36, Folder 40)
  - Western Coalitions
    - Alaska
      - Alaska, 1993-1994 (Box 36, Folder 41)
    - Arizona
      - Phoenix, AZ, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 42)
      - Phoenix, AZ, 1997-1998 (Box 36, Folder 43)
      - Arizona - Phoenix, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 44)
      - Phoenix JWJ, 1993-1996 (Box 36, Folder 45)
      - SAAEJ, 2001-2002 (Box 36, Folder 46)
      - Tucson, 2000-2001 (Box 36, Folder 47)
      - Tucson JWJ, 2000 (Box 36, Folder 48)
      - Tucson, AZ, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 49)
      - Tucson, AZ, 1997-1998 (Box 36, Folder 50)
      - Tucson - Brush Wellman WRB Hearing, 2000 (Box 36, Folder 51)
      - Tucson Trip, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 52)
      - SAAEJ/Arizona JWJ, 2000 (Box 36, Folder 53)
      - Arizona, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 54)
      - Arizona, 2001-2002 (Box 36, Folder 55)
    - California
      - Fresno Labor/Community Alliance Newsletter, 2001-01-2001-10 (Box 41, Folder 1)
      - Fresno JWJ, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 2)
      - International Workers Day in Fresno, 2002-04-29 (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - Fresno, CA, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 4-5)
      - Orange County, CA Workers for Justice and Democracy, 1992-1993 (Box 41, Folder 6)
      - San Diego JWJ, 1992-1999 (Box 41, Folder 7)
      - South Bay, CA (Box 41, Folder 8)
      - CA interest in JWJ, 1996-2002 (Box 41, Folder 9)
      - Fresno JWJ, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Colorado
      - Denver, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 11-12)
      - Denver, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 13)
      - Denver, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 14)
      - Colorado JWJ, 2002-2004 (Box 41, Folder 15-16)
      - CO Planning Retreat, 1996 (Box 41, Folder 17)
      - Colorado, 1998-1999 (Box 41, Folder 18)
      - Colorado JWJ, 1994-1998 (Box 41, Folder 19)
      - Colorado JWJ, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 20)
      - Colorado JWJ, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 21)
      - Colorado Supporting Unions Campaign, 1998-1999 (Box 41, Folder 22)
      - JWJ 12th Anniversary Invitation, 1999-06-09 (Box 41, Folder 23)
      - Denver: WRB, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 24)
      - Englewood, 1997-1998 (Box 41, Folder 25)
      - Colorado JWJ Newsletter, 1995-1996 (Box 41, Folder 26)
      - Take Back Your Future: A Worker's Rights Handbook, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 27)
      - Colorado, 2001-2003 (Box 41, Folder 28)
      - CO, 2001-2002 (Box 41, Folder 29)
      - CO WRB, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 30)
    - Montana
      - Montana - notes, 2001-2003 (Box 41, Folder 31)
      - Montana, 1996-2002 (Box 41, Folder 32)
      - Montana, 2002-2003 (Box 41, Folder 33)
      - Missoula, MT, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 34)
      - Montana Community Labor All. "I'll be There", 1995-1998 (Box 41, Folder 35)
      - Missoula, MT, 1997-1998 (Box 41, Folder 36)
      - Montana Community-Labor Alliance, 1994-1997 (Box 41, Folder 37)
    - New Mexico
      - New Mexico, 2001-12-11 (Box 41, Folder 38)
      - New Mexico, 2001-2002 (Box 41, Folder 39)
        CD
    - Oregon
      - Portland JWJ, 1998-2000 (Box 41, Folder 47)
      - ESSN, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 48)
      - ESSN, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 49)
      - ESSN/JWJ, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 50)
      - ESSN, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 51)
      - Portland JWJ, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 52)
      - Eugene, OR, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 53)
      - Eugene, OR, 1997-1998 (Box 41, Folder 54)
      - Eugene, OR Solidarity Network, 1993-1997 (Box 41, Folder 55)
      - Eugene, OR Solidarity Network Newsletter, 1993-10-1996-12 (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - ESSN, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Tidewater, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - Tidewater, 1998-2000 (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Portland, OR JWJ, 1993-2000 (Box 34, Folder 5)
        floppy discs (2)
      - Mid-Willamette JWJ, 1999-2001 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - Mid-Willamette, OR, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - Portland, OR Direct Action + JWJ, 1994-1995 (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - Salem, OR, 1997-1998 (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - Portland, OR, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 10)
      - Portland JWJ, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 11)
      - Portland JWJ, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 12)
      - Portland JWJ + WRB, 2003 (Box 34, Folder 13-14)
      - Eugene, 2000-2004 (Box 34, Folder 15)
      - Portland, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 16)
      - Portland, 1999-2001 (Box 34, Folder 17-18)
      - Portland, 2002-2003 (Box 34, Folder 19)
      - Portland Workers' Rights, 2002-2004 (Box 34, Folder 20)
      - Mid-Willamette Valley, 2000-2001 (Box 34, Folder 21)
      - Portland, OR, 1997-1998 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - South Dakota
      - South Dakota, 1999-02-18 (Box 41, Folder 40)
    - Utah
      - Utah, 2002-2003 (Box 41, Folder 41)
      - UT, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 42)
      - Utah- Salt Lake City JWJ, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 43)
      - Salt Lake City, 1999-2002 (Box 41, Folder 44-45)
      - Utah, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 46)
    - Washington
      - Washington State, 2002-2003 (Box 34, Folder 23)
      - Wash State JWJ, 2001-2002 (Box 34, Folder 24)
      - Seattle, WA, 1997-1998 (Box 34, Folder 25-26)
      - Washington State JWJ, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 27)
      - Washing State JWJ, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 28)
      - Washington State Labor Council, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 29)
      - Seattle, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 30)
      - Washington State JWJ, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 31)
      - Seattle, 2001-2004 (Box 34, Folder 32-34)
        photo in frame in 34 -- too big for photo sleeve
      - Washington State JWJ, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 35)
        floppy disc in envelope (back of folder)
      - Washington State JWJ, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 36)
      - Washington JWJ, 1999-2001 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Nancy/Budget, 2002-2003 (Box 23, Folder 2-3)
      - Voter Reg., 2004 (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - Angelina Research Project, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Washington Policies, 2006 (Box 51, Folder 51)
      - Washington, 2001-2002 (Box 51, Folder 55)
  - Southern Coalitions
    - Southern Coalitions, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 6-10)
    - Southern Coalitions Binder #2, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 11-13)
    - Alabama
      - Alabama JWJ, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Arkansas
      - Fayetteville, Arkansas, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 14)
      - AK JWJ, 1999-03-23 (Box 23, Folder 15)
      - Arkansas, 1997-1999 (Box 23, Folder 16)
      - Arkansas JWJ, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 17)
      - Little Rock AR, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Florida
      - Miami, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 34)
      - Miami, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 35)
      - Miami, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 36-37)
      - Miami JWJ, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 38)
      - Miami, 2000 (Box 48, Folder 1)
      - Miami Planning Retreat, 2001 (Box 48, Folder 2)
      - Miami - Living wage + 99 background JWJ, 1999 (Box 48, Folder 3)
      - Central Florida JWJ, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 19)
      - C. FL JWJ, 2011-2014 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Georgia
      - JWJ Committee of the Atlanta Labor Council, 1999 (Box 48, Folder 4)
      - Atlanta, 1988 (Box 48, Folder 5)
      - Atlanta, 2001 (Box 48, Folder 6)
      - Atlanta, GA JWJ, 1999-2000 (Box 48, Folder 7)
      - Atlanta Labor Council, 1999 (Box 48, Folder 8)
      - Atlanta, GA, 1997-1998 (Box 23, Folder 22)
      - Atlanta, GA Labor Council, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 23)
      - Atlanta, GA Labor Council, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 24)
      - Atlanta, GA Labor Council, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 25)
      - Atlanta, GA Labor Council, 1992-1993 (Box 23, Folder 26)
      - ATL JWJ, 2012-2015 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Kentucky
      - International Day of Action, 2000-09-26 (Box 22, Folder 18)
      - Labor Forum on Merger, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 19)
      - Louisville, KY, 1997-1998 (Box 22, Folder 20)
      - Louisville JWJ, 1997-1998 (Box 22, Folder 21-22)
      - Kentucky JWJ - Louisville, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 23-24)
        floppy disc - back of folder 23
      - Kentucky $$ + Staffing, 2003-2004 (Box 22, Folder 25)
      - Kentucky JWJ, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 26-27)
      - Kentucky, 2001-2003 (Box 22, Folder 28)
      - Kentucky, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 29)
      - KY Econ Justice, 1997-03 (Box 22, Folder 30)
      - Louisville, KY JWJ, 1992-1996 (Box 23, Folder 27)
        floppy disc in orange envelope
      - Louisville - Tyson Strike, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 28)
      - Louisville, KY, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 29)
      - KY JWJ, 2015 (Box 51, Folder 8)
        mini DVD-RW
    - Louisiana
      - NOLA, 2011-2014 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Mississippi
      - Mississippi South Central Labor Union, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - North Carolina
      - North Carolina JWJ, 2000 (Box 48, Folder 9)
      - North Carolina, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 10)
      - Greensboro NC, 1999 (Box 48, Folder 11)
      - North Carolina, 1998 (Box 48, Folder 12)
      - Greensboro, NC, 1997-1998 (Box 48, Folder 13)
      - Grassroots Leadership, 1997 (Box 48, Folder 14)
      - North Carolina, 1999 (Box 48, Folder 15)
      - NC Triad JWJ, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 20)
      - Black Workers for Justice, 1994-1996 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Tennessee
      - Tennessee, 2003-07-15 (Box 23, Folder 35)
      - TN JWJ, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 31)
      - Tennessee JWJ - Knoxville, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 32)
      - Knoxville, TN, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 33)
      - Knoxville, TN, 1997-1998 (Box 23, Folder 30)
      - Nashville, TN, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 31)
      - Nashville, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 32)
      - Middle TN, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 36)
      - Middle Tennessee JWJ Nashville, 1995-1996 (Box 23, Folder 33)
        floppy disc in white envelope
      - Nashville, TN, 1997-1998 (Box 23, Folder 34)
      - Nashville, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - Texas
      - North Texas JWJ Update, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - North Texas JWJ Workers Rights Board, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - North Texas JWJ, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - North Texas JWJ, 1994-1996 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - North Texas, 1991-2001 (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - Dallas JWJ, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - Dallas, 2001-2003 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - Dallas JWJ, 2000-2003 (Box 19, Folder 11)
      - Dallas, TX, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 12)
      - Dallas, TX, 1997-1998 (Box 19, Folder 13)
      - San Antonio, TX, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - San Antonio, TX, 1997-1998 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - Austin, TX, 1997-12-10 (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - Austin Cable Vision, 2001 (Box 52, Folder 55)
    - Virginia
      - North Virginia, 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Files of Southern Regional Field Organizer Dyana Forester
      - South FL, 2012 (Box 48, Folder 68)
      - South Carolina, 2011-2014 (Box 48, Folder 69)
      - Group Exemption Details, 2008-2010 (Box 48, Folder 70)
      - A state of fear: Human rights abuses in North Carolina's tobacco industry, 2011 (Box 48, Folder 71)
      - Immigrants in the U.S. South, 2013-11 (Box 48, Folder 72)
      - Keys to Revolution: Organizing Black Workers and Communities in the South, 2014-04-28-2014-04-29 (Box 48, Folder 73)
      - 9th Bi-annual southern Human Rights Organizers' Conference, 2012-12-07-2012-12-09 (Box 48, Folder 74)
      - KY JWJ, 2012-2014 (Box 48, Folder 75-76)
      - N. Texas, 2015 (Box 48, Folder 77)
      - N. Texas, 2014 (Box 48, Folder 78)
      - NC RDU, 2009-2013 (Box 48, Folder 79)
      - NC Triad, 2013 (Box 48, Folder 80)
      - M. TN Nashville, undated (Box 48, Folder 81)
      - E. TN Knoxville, 2013-2016 (Box 48, Folder 82)
      - Moral Mondays, 2013-2014 (Box 48, Folder 83)
      - Expansion Notes, 2010-2011 (Box 48, Folder 84)
        DVD
  - Mid-Atlantic Coalitions
    - DC
      - Washington DC - Local JWJ, 1996-2001 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - DC JWJ, 2011-2016 (Box 51, Folder 5-6)
      - DC JWJ, 2016 (Box 51, Folder 7)
      - DC, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 56)
    - West Virginia
      - West Virginia, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Northeast Coalitions
    - Northeast Field Organizer Binder, 2009 (Box 22, Folder 15-16)
    - Northeast Local Coalition Development Goals, 2004 (Box 51, Folder 47)
    - Northeast Regional Goals, 2008 (Box 51, Folder 48)
    - Northeast Priorities, 2006 (Box 51, Folder 49)
    - Connecticut
      - Connecticut OC, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 13)
      - Connecticut, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Maine
      - Maine, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 23)
      - Maine, 2006-2009 (Box 21, Folder 24)
      - Maine, 2013-2014 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Massachusetts
      - Boston, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 15)
      - Boston RTO, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 16)
      - Boston: WRB, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 17)
      - Western MA, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 18)
      - Massachusetts Jobs with Justice, 1996-1999 (Box 20, Folder 19)
      - Boston, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 20-21)
      - Western Mass., 1999 (Box 20, Folder 22)
      - Western Mass, 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 23)
      - Western Massachusetts JWJ Workers' Rights Board, 1995-1996 (Box 20, Folder 24)
      - Western Massachusetts JWJ, 1995-2002 (Box 20, Folder 25)
      - Boston JWJ Campaign, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 26)
      - Massachusetts JWJ Workers' Rights Board, 1995-1996 (Box 20, Folder 27)
      - W. Mass: WRB, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 28)
      - Boston, MA, 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 29-31)
      - Massachusetts JWJ, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 32)
      - Boston Planning Retreat, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 33)
      - Massachusetts - Merrimack Valley JWJ, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 34)
      - West. Mass, 2002-2003 (Box 20, Folder 35)
      - W. Mass JWJ, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 38)
      - Western Mass JWJ, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 39)
      - Massachusetts JWJ, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 40)
      - Massachusetts JWJ, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 41)
      - E MA, 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - Massachusetts JWJ, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - Massachusetts JWJ, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - Boston, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - Boston JWJ, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 5-6)
      - Massachusetts JWJ, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 7)
      - Eastern Mass, 2012-2016 (Box 21, Folder 8)
      - E MA JWJ, 2008-01-2009-10 (Box 21, Folder 9)
      - Eastern MA JWJ Check-Ins, 2003-2004 (Box 21, Folder 10)
      - MA Statewide, 2014-2015 (Box 21, Folder 11)
      - Boston, 2005-01-2008-12 (Box 21, Folder 12)
      - Boston Fundraising + Finances, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 13)
      - Mass. Health Care Const. Amendment Campaign, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 14)
      - Healthcare for Massachusetts Campaign Strategy Meeting, 2006-01-25 (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - E MA JWJ, 2000-2002 (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - West Mass JWJ, 2010-2016 (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - W. MA, 2007-2009 (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - W. Mass JWJ, 2005-01-2007 (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - W Mass WRB Staff, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Intelicoat Campaign Originals, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - MA JWJ, 2005-2007 (Box 21, Folder 22)
      - Health Care Action week, 2004-10 (Box 52, Folder 56)
    - New Hampshire
      - N.H., 1991-05-02 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - New Jersey
      - New Jersey, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 52)
      - New Jersey, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 53)
      - New Jersey, 2007-2008 (Box 19, Folder 54)
      - Trenton - New Jersey, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 55)
      - New Jersey JWJ, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 56)
      - New Jersey, 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - New jersey Citizen Action, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - New York
      - NYS statewide, 2013-2015 (Box 17, Folder 15)
      - NYS Alliance Planning, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 16)
      - NYS, 2007-01-2009 (Box 17, Folder 17)
      - NYS, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 18)
      - NYS Gathering, 2005-06-22 (Box 17, Folder 19)
      - NY Statewide Work, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 20)
      - Albany
        - Albany, NY, 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 5-6)
        - Albany, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 7)
        - Albany, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 8)
        - Albany Solidarity Committee of the Capital District, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 9)
        - Albany JWJ, 2002-03-05 (Box 18, Folder 10)
        - Albany, NY Solidarity Comm., Solidarity Notes, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 11)
        - Albany Solidarity Committee, Solidarity Notes, 1993-1997 (Box 18, Folder 12)
        - Albany, NY Solidarity Committee of the Capital District, 1995-1996 (Box 18, Folder 13)
        - Domestic Workers' Bill of Rights Albany Day 2008 (Box 18, Folder 14)
        - Albany, 2007-01-2009-10 (Box 18, Folder 15)
        - Albany, 2005-01-2006-12 (Box 18, Folder 16)
        - Albany, 2003-2005 (Box 18, Folder 17)
        - Albany - Samples and Clips, 2004-2005 (Box 18, Folder 18)
      - Buffalo
        - Buffalo Materials, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 19)
        - Buffalo, 2005-01-2006-02 (Box 18, Folder 20-21)
        - New York, 2001-2003 (Box 18, Folder 22)
        - Buffalo, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 23)
        - Student Labor Organizing, 2012 (Box 18, Folder 24)
        - Buffalo: WRB, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 25)
        - Buffalo, NY, 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 26-27)
        - Buffalo Coalition for Economic Justice Workers' Rights Board, 1995-1997 (Box 18, Folder 28)
        - Buffalo, NY JWJ, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 29)
        - Buffalo, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 30)
        - Buffalo, NY Coalition for Economic Justice, 1994-1999 (Box 18, Folder 31)
        - Buffalo, 2007-01-2009-10 (Box 18, Folder 32)
        - The $7,000000 Wager: NY State's Costly Gamble in Economic Development, 2013-05 (Box 17, Folder 1)
        - Achieving a Greater Buffalo, 2007-04 (Box 17, Folder 2)
        - Council on Occupational Safety and Health + CEJ Anniversary Banquet, 2004-06-18 (Box 17, Folder 3)
        - Coalition for Economic Justice (CEJ), 2012-2016 (Box 19, Folder 15)
        - CEJ Board Retreat, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 16)
        - CEJ Program + Updates, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 17)
        - CEJ Strategic Planning, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 18)
        - CEJ Fundraising/Finances, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 19)
      - Long Island
        - LI JWJ, 2016 (Box 20, Folder 4)
        - Long Island, 2012-2015 (Box 20, Folder 5)
        - LI JWJ 2009 Transition (Box 20, Folder 6)
        - LI JWJ, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 7)
        - L.I. JWJ, 2007-01-2008-12 (Box 20, Folder 8)
        - Long Island, 2005-01-2006-12 (Box 20, Folder 9)
        - Long Island JWJ OC, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 10)
        - Long Island JWJ/Coalition to Save LI Jobs, 2002-2003 (Box 20, Folder 11)
        - Long Island, 2000-2001 (Box 20, Folder 12)
        - Long Island JWJ, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 13)
        - Long Island, NY, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 14)
      - New York City
        - Metro Justice, 2008-2009 (Box 17, Folder 21)
        - NYC JWJ, 2007-01-2009-10 (Box 17, Folder 22)
        - NYC, 2005-01-2006-12 (Box 17, Folder 23)
        - NYC JWJ, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 24)
        - NYC JWJ, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 25)
        - NYC WRB, 2000-2001 (Box 17, Folder 26)
        - 10/30 Newsday Article NY JWJ Hearing, 2001-10-30 (Box 17, Folder 27)
        - New York City, NY, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 28)
        - NYC JWJ, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 29)
        - NYC WRB, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 30)
        - NYC, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 31)
        - New York City: WRB, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 33)
        - New York City Workers' Rights Board, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 34)
        - New York City JWJ, 1995-1996 (Box 17, Folder 35)
        - New York City JWJ, 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 36)
        - New York City JWJ, 1991-1992 (Box 17, Folder 37)
        - NYC JWJ, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 38-40)
        - Health Care - New York Jobs with Justice, 1992-1995 (Box 17, Folder 41)
        - New York City JWJ, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 42)
        - ALIGN, 2012-2015 (Box 17, Folder 43)
        - New York JWJ Board of Directors Meeting, 2003-02-06 (Box 17, Folder 44)
        - Is your Gourmet Grocery a Sweatshop?, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 45)
        - "Finding the Courage" 2005 Awards Night, 2005-05-03 (Box 17, Folder 46)
        - NYC Health Care Security Act, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 47)
        - JWJ Circle of Activists, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 48)
        - Climate Works for All, 2015 (Box 20, Folder 1)
        - ALIGN - Caring Across New York City, 2013-08 (Box 20, Folder 2)
        - One Future One City, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - Upstate NY
        - Syracuse JWJ, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 4)
        - Syracuse, NY, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 5)
        - TCWC, 2012-2017 (Box 17, Folder 6)
        - Ithaca, 2001-2009 (Box 17, Folder 7)
        - Syracuse, 2006-08-25 (Box 17, Folder 8)
        - Binghamton, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 9)
        - Rochester, 2005-01 (Box 17, Folder 10)
        - Mid-Hudson, 2005-01 (Box 17, Folder 11)
        - Mid-Hudson Valley, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 12)
        - Rochester, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 13)
        - Syracuse/other new sites, 2003-2005 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Pennsylvania
      - Philadelphia, 2011-2016 (Box 19, Folder 20)
      - Philadelphia, 2009 (Box 19, Folder 21)
      - Philadelphia, 2007-01-2008-12 (Box 19, Folder 22-23)
      - Philadelphia Planning, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 24)
      - Philadelphia, 2005-01-2006-12 (Box 19, Folder 25)
      - Philadelphia- JWJ/SEIU meeting, 2005-2006 (Box 19, Folder 26)
      - Philadelphia JWJ Check-Ins, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 27)
      - Philadelphia Foundation Grant Proposals + Budgets, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 28)
      - Pittsburgh, 2007-01 (Box 19, Folder 29)
      - Pittsburgh, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 30)
      - Erie, PA, 2003-2004 (Box 19, Folder 31)
      - Pittsburgh, 2001-2002 (Box 19, Folder 32-33)
      - Pittsburgh, 2003-2004 (Box 19, Folder 34)
      - Pittsburgh, 2002-05 (Box 19, Folder 35)
      - Philadelphia, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 36)
      - Philadelphia, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 37)
      - Philadelphia, 2002-2003 (Box 19, Folder 38)
      - Philadelphia, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 39)
      - Philadelphia, 1999-2002 (Box 19, Folder 40)
      - Pittsburgh, 2002-2003 (Box 19, Folder 41)
      - Pittsburgh, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 42)
      - Pittsburgh, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 43)
      - A.P.A. Pittsburgh, 1998-1999 (Box 19, Folder 44)
      - Pittsburgh, 1997-1998 (Box 19, Folder 45)
      - Alliance for Progressive Action Update, Fall 1992 (Box 19, Folder 46)
      - Pittsburgh, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 47)
      - Pennsylvania JWJ, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 48)
      - Pennsylvania JWJ, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 49)
      - Miscellaneous, 2002-2003 (Box 19, Folder 50)
      - Grow Receipts (USAS), 2002 (Box 19, Folder 51)
    - Rhode Island
      - Rhode Island, 2012-2013 (Box 21, Folder 36)
      - Rhode Island JWJ, 2010-2011 (Box 21, Folder 36)
      - Camilo Viveros Letters, 2011 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - RI, 2009 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Colibri, 2009 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - RI JWJ, 2007-01-2008-12 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Rhode Island, 2005-01-2006-12 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Immigrants United, 2006-05-01 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Rhode Island Finances + Fundraising, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - Rhode Island Check-Ins, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - Rhode Island, 2002-2003 (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - Providence, RI, 1997-1998 (Box 22, Folder 10)
      - Rhode Island JWJ, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 11)
      - RI JWJ, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 36)
      - Rhode Island JWJ, 1996-2000 (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - Vermont
      - Vermont JWJ, 1992-1996 (Box 21, Folder 26)
      - Vermont, 2002-2003 (Box 21, Folder 27)
      - VT, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 28)
      - Vermont Healthcare Actions Summit, 2005-02-10 (Box 21, Folder 29)
      - Vermont Worker Center, 2012-2016 (Box 21, Folder 30)
      - Vermont, 2007-01-2009-10 (Box 21, Folder 31)
      - Vermont, 2005-2006-12 (Box 21, Folder 32)
      - VWC Materials, 2004-2005 (Box 21, Folder 33)
      - Vermont Workers' Center Finances/Fundraising, 2004-2005 (Box 21, Folder 34)
      - Vermont Workers' Center Check-Ins, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - State Charters
    - JWJ Charter Process, 2002-2003 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Charter Memos, 2003-06-09 (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - Charter Process, 2002-2003 (Box 48, Folder 19)
    - Charter Applications, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 20)
    - North Texas, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 21)
    - Philadelphia, 2002-12 (Box 48, Folder 22)
    - Pittsburgh, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 23)